

britta rodenbeck front-end & ui developer

web brittarodenbeck.com
email cheers@brittarodenbeck.com
phone (815) 222 - 8436

profile

I am a web developer specializing in front-end development and design, experienced with all stages of the development cycle from product conception to design, development, testing, deployment, and maintenance. I have a passion for web applications with engaging and beautiful user interfaces with practical user experiences.

education

Grand Circus Detroit

Front-end development bootcamp *Yune 2016*

Northern Illinois University

Psychological sciences *December 2014*

competencies

JavaScript ES6/ES7, Vue.js/ Vuex, Nuxt, React/Redux

CSS CSS3, Sass, Stylus, Bootstrap, UI Kit, Bulma, CSS/ SVG animations

Design Responsive design, Sketch, Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, & InDesign, Figma

Tooling Git, GitHub, Netlify, Webpack, NPM, Yarn, VSCode

experience

Lead Front-End Developer, Argonomo LLC

Specializing in rapid prototyping of front-end websites and applications using Vue.js and React. Responsible for architecting, designing, and developing web applications for clients in fields from blockchain, mobility, medical tech, and more. Collaborating with business developers, designers, and SEO specialists to create a cohesive brand and product for clients and equity partners alike. *March 2018 - Present*

Lead UI Engineer, Career Now Brands

Collaborated with lead developer and design/product teams to implement front-end solutions and builds for 20+ web properties and applications with a focus on user interface and user experience using Vue.js. Used Asana and GitHub to self-manage productivity on projects for optimal workflow to meet strict deadlines. *September 2017 - February 2018*

Full-Stack Web Developer, Career Now Brands

Responsible for designing, developing, and maintaining 20+ web applications and properties. Lead a team to complete end-to-end design and development for web property responsible for matching prospective students with CDL training facilities nationwide utilizing Laravel and Vue.js. Collaborated with Paid Media team to execute A/B testing on pay-per-click social media outreach campaigns. *July 2016 - September 2017*